This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption
and shameful acts are not encouraged.
Please view this as a comedy.
Furthermore, all characters appearing
in this work are of legal age.
（伊織(いおり)）マズい…
This is bad...
You're the only one who's going to fail.
（奈々華(ななか)）伊織君だけ
不合格になっちゃうかも
（伊織）
まさかの俺だけ不合格
No way. I'm the only one who's going to fail?
If they find out...
この事実を
やつらに知られたら…
（愛菜(あいな)と耕平(こうへい)の笑い声）
I'll die of embarrassment!
死に勝る屈辱
You're not good at mask clearing.
伊織君は 特に
マスククリアが苦手みたいだね
Luckily, I have a mask.
（伊織）
幸い マスクなら持ってる
And there's a pool and the ocean nearby.
プールも海も近くにある
The only problem is how to practice
without those guys finding out.
問題は いかに
やつらにバレずに練習するかだ
I can't get them drunk or lock them up.
（伊織）潰すのは無理
拘束は場所が…
（千紗(ちさ)）あっ 伊織？
-Iori?
-I can knock them out.
But it's dinner time now.
（千紗）ん？
（伊織）ハッ！
Maybe I could poison them!
毒殺したらいいのか！
What are you smiling about?
いい笑顔で 何言ってるの
Chisa! It's not nice to eavesdrop!
あっ 千紗！
盗み聞きとは趣味が悪いぞ
Not as bad as poisoning people.
毒殺ほどじゃないと思うけど
Hey! We're going to go rent a car.
（時田(ときた)）おーい
車 借りに行くぞ
We're going to the market.
（寿(ことぶき)）市場まで買い出しだ！
Hey, Chisa! They're calling you.
あ… ほら 千紗 呼ばれてるぞ！
（千紗）あっ…
He's acting suspicious.
怪しい…
♪～
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
GRAND BLUE DREAMING
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
～♪
All right. Use this.
（店主）
じゃ こいつ 使ってくれや
What's wrong?
（店主）どうしたば 兄ちゃんたち
What does it look like?
（伊織）どうしたも こうしたも
How are we all supposed to fit in this?
（耕平）これに どうやって
全員乗れと？
Tokki, did you mess up the reservation?
（梓(あずさ)）トッキー 予約 間違えた？
No. I made the right reservation.
（時田）いや
ちゃんと予約してあるが
Oh, I mixed up four people and eight people.
あっさー ４人と８人を
間違えてしまったさあ
How can you mix that up?
（伊織）普通 そこ間違えるか!?
Sorry, sorry.
悪い悪い
I'll get another car.
今 別の車 用意しようね
（耕平）別の車？
Another car?
As an apology,
間違えたおわびに―
I'm going to give you a convertible
with lots of room in the back seat!
後ろが広いオープンカーを
タダで貸してあげるさ　フフッ
-Seriously?
-A convertible?
マジで!?
（愛菜）オープンカー!?
-How is it?
-Well, there is lots of room.
どうね？
（伊織）確かに広いな
-It feels liberating.
-So, no problems.
開放感も この上ないな
問題なしっと
（伊織）いやいやいや！
-No, no, no!
-Bring the car for eight people!
普通に８人乗り持ってこいよ！
We don't have big cars like that here.
そんな大きな車
うちにはないよ～
What's wrong with this shop?
なんなんだよ この店は！
Have a nice trip!
（店主）それじゃ よい旅を！
-What?
-Hey, old man!
（伊織）ああっ!?
（耕平）おっさん！
What are we going to do?
どうすんだよ これ…
This car is manual.
この車 マニュアルだぞ
-Sorry. I forgot to bring my license.
-Me too.
すまん 免許 忘れてきちまった
（寿）俺も…
I can only drive automatics.
私はオートマ限定だし…
フフッ…
フッ 短い人生だったなあ
Life is short.
The sky is so blue.
空が あんなにも青い
You guys are so rude!
あんたら ほんとに失礼ね！
Wow, this is a good ride!
おお これはこれで
乗り心地 いいな
Hey! I forgot to tell you.
（店主）ああ 兄ちゃんたち
言い忘れてたけど
（一同）ん？
The roads here are all on private land.
ここから先 走る道路は
全部 私有地だからね
This old guy really has some nerve.
（伊織）堂々と すげえこと
言ってんぞ このおっさん
-Bye!
-Here we go!
じゃあ…
（愛菜）それじゃ 行きますよ
Everyone, hold on to something!
みんな 何かにつかまれ！
（伊織）え？
（耕平）ケバ子が―
Cakey is driving a manual?
マニュアル車を
普通に走らせてるだと？
She's really used to it.
（寿）ずいぶん
慣れてる感じだなあ
How come you're so used to manuals?
なぜ そんなに慣れている？
え？　な 慣れてなんか…
I'm not used to it!
Well, this is amazing.
いや 見事なもんだぞ
No way!
ま まさか 都会の似合う
うちが―
Are you trying to say that a city girl like me
drove a car to help out in rice fields?
車で畑ん手伝いば
しよったとでも？
I see. So that's why.
（伊織）
なるほど そういうことか
Then we have nothing to worry about.
（時田）それなら安心だな
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner
is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing
as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence
or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised.
Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products
is intended. The Content Provider, the producers
and related parties shall have no liability,
as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability
for any purpose of the information provided in this work.
The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect
the views and opinions of the Content Provider,
or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
（伊織たちの笑い声）
-This isn't bad!
-Yeah!
案外 これもいいもんですね
（寿）おう！
-I feel like having a beer.
-Yeah.
しかし こうなると―
ビールを飲みたくなるなあ
（耕平）だなあ
At least wait until tonight!
せめて 夜まで我慢しなさーい！
（耕平）むっ！　対向車だ
（伊織）ヤバい 隠れろ！
-An oncoming car.
-This is bad. Hide!
（運転手）ん？
ヒイイッ！
Great! No problem.
よしっ！　問題ないな
It didn't look like anyone was riding back here.
確かに 今のなら 人が
乗っているようには見えませんよね
It just looked like a normal truck carrying a few corpses.
死体を運搬している 普通の
軽トラにしか見えないもんなあ
（伊織たちの笑い声）
（愛菜）何やってんの！
What are you doing?
（梓）アハハハ
（千紗）何やってんだか…
What are they doing?
All right. Pick something you'd like to eat.
（時田）それじゃ 各自
食いたい食材を適当に選んで
When we get back, let's each make a dish!
帰ったら みんなで
１品ずつ作ろうぜ！
Oh, nice idea.
おお いいねえ！
-All right. Good luck!
-Yeah!
（時田）では 健闘を祈る
（一同）おーっ！
Lalako-tan!
（耕平）ららこたーん！
There's lots of unusual things here.
（愛菜）珍しい物がいっぱいだね
うん
It tests our ability to choose ingredients.
これは食材選びのセンスが
試されるな
I wonder what the guys are going to choose.
先輩たちは何にするんだろ…
（愛菜）ギャッ！　うわっ！
あっ 大丈夫？
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'll go ask them.
あっ うん
じゃあ 私が聞いてくるよ
Welcome! What would you like?
（店員）へい らっしゃい
何にしやす？
-Oh, there you are.
-I...
あっ いた
（梓）えっと 私は―
want to eat an old man.
オジサンが食べたいなあ
ええっ!?
（愛菜）ああ…
（耕平）どうした？　ケバ子
What's wrong, Cakey?
What happened?
（千紗）何かあったの？
Azusa...
あ… 梓さんが…
was trying to eat the old man at the fish stall.
魚屋のおじさんを
食べようとしてた
An old man at a fish stall?
（千紗）魚屋のおじさん？
What did you see?
（耕平）
お前は 何を見てきたんだ？
ううん！　今のはきっと
何かの聞き間違い！
I probably just heard wrong.
Really?
そ… そうか
Then that's good.
（千紗）それならいいけど
（愛菜）あ…
-I'm going to ask Tokita.
-Okay.
次は 時田先輩に聞いてくる
（千紗）うん
I don't get what's going on. Just go.
よく分からんが 行ってこい
（愛菜）あの…
（時田）ああ そうなんだ 俺は…
-Um...
-Oh, I see. I...
want Hamasaki's wife.
浜崎(はまさき)の奧さんが欲しい
（愛菜）ゴフッ！
（愛菜）うう…
（千紗）愛菜？
-Aina?
-Tokita...
（愛菜）時田先輩が…
（耕平）あの人がどうした？
What about him?
-Tokita was trying to get with a married woman.
-Hold on.
（愛菜）人妻に手を出そうと…
（千紗）ちょっと待って
What did you hear just now?
（耕平）お前は さっきから
何を聞いてる
Maybe you heard wrong.
何かの聞き間違いじゃないの？
I heard it clearly!
（愛菜）
でも この耳ではっきりと！
You must be hearing things.
だとしたら幻聴だな
Then let's go and find out together.
（愛菜）じゃ みんなで行って
確認しようよ
I don't mind.
別にいいけど
Oh, dear.
やれやれ…
（愛菜）あっ
Welcome! What are you looking for?
（店員）いらっしゃい！
何をお探しで？
He's just shopping like normal.
普通の買い物だね
There's nothing weird going on.
何も おかしなところはないな
You think so?
そ… そうかな
You must have misunderstood, Aina.
やっぱり 愛菜の勘違いじゃない？
そもそも こんな場所で
妙なまねをするとは思えん
They wouldn't do anything weird in a place like this.
うっ… 確かに
You're right.
-We have everything. Just tell me what you're looking for.
-All right.
うちは なんでもそろってるよ
遠慮なく言ってくれ
（寿）それじゃあ―
A chubby high school student.
肉づきのいい高校生を
（耕平･愛菜）アウト～！
Out!
What's he trying to buy here?
（耕平）こんなところで
何を買う気だ!?
I told you!
（愛菜）だから言ったでしょ！
ここは 通報するべきか…
Should we turn him in?
We should talk to him first.
その前に 一応
事情を聞いたほうが…
Wait, you two.
（千紗）待って ２人とも
（愛菜･耕平）あ…
-I think you guys have the wrong idea.
-What?
（千紗）たぶん それ
勘違いだと思う
（耕平･愛菜）え？
Those are all names of fish.
（千紗）それ全部
魚の名前だから
そうなの？
-Really?
-What amazing names!
すごいネーミングセンスだな…
Then what Azusa and Tokita said just now...
じゃあ さっきの梓さんも
時田先輩も…
-They were trying to buy fish?
-Yeah.
魚を買おうとしていたと…
（千紗）うん
Of course, they wouldn't actually
try to buy stuff like that.
真剣に考えたら
そんなの買うわけないよね
Well... I knew what was going on all along.
（耕平）まあ 俺は最初から
分かっていたがな
You were surprised too.
（愛菜）思いっきり
一緒に驚いてたくせに
-Excuse me.
-Hi, welcome.
（伊織）すみません
（店員）あいよ いらっしゃい！
I need a poisonous fish
that can knock an adult out with one bite.
一口で 成人がこん倒するような
毒魚を１匹
（店員）ねえよ んなもん
We don't sell things like that here.
It's not nice spying on people while they shop!
（伊織）人の買い物を
のぞき見とは 趣味が悪いぞ
You're the one who was trying to buy a poisonous fish!
（耕平）毒魚を買おうと
したやつが 何を言うか！
You're planning something weird again!
絶対 また何か変なこと
たくらんでるでしょ！
It didn't work. If I don't do something...
（伊織）チッ 失敗か
このままだと…
（愛菜と耕平の笑い声）
I'm going to end up dying of embarrassment!
死ぬほどの恥辱を
受けるはめに…
Okay, everybody draw one.
はい みんなも１本引いて
（千紗）ん？
（愛菜）なんですか？　これ
What for?
It's to decide who cooks first.
料理の順番を決めるくじだよ
（伊織）あ…
We won't all fit in the kitchen.
キッチンに 全員は
入れないからな
-We're going to take turns cooking in pairs.
-That's why.
２人ずつで順番にやろうってわけだ
（梓）そゆこと
I just have to draw one, right?
（愛菜）１本引けば
いいんですね
（伊織）ん？
２人一緒で調理？
Cooking in pairs?
ハッ！　ということは―
That means if I can get Kohei paired up with Cakey...
このくじで 耕平とケバ子を
セットにしたら
I can practice while they're cooking!
やつらが調理してる間は
練習できる！
-I'm number four.
-I'm number two.
私 ４番
私は２番
あっ… ん？
Please pair me up with Chisa.
（伊織）千紗と一緒でお願いします
千紗と一緒でお願いします
Please pair me up with Chisa.
千紗と一緒でお願いします…
-Iori?
-Please, God!
い… 伊織？
（伊織）頼む 神様！　どうか！
Please!
Yeah!
よっしゃあ～！
Hey, Chisa! We're paired up!
さあ 千紗
一緒のペアだぞ！
Aina, That guy is gross. Can you switch with me?
愛菜 気持ち悪いから替わって
（愛菜）え？
Why are you saying that, Chisa?
なぜ そんなことを言うんだ
千紗！
We'll have fun cooking together as a pair!
俺とお前のペアで
楽しく料理を作ろうぜっ！
-He is gross.
-What are you going to do?
確かに キモいな…
（愛菜）どうするの？
I'm going to hold onto the knife the whole time.
調理中は
ずっと包丁 握ってる
Iori, you went overboard.
（梓）伊織 やりすぎだよ
（伊織）へっ？
な… 何がですか？
What do you mean?
No way. Did Azusa notice?
（伊織）まさか 梓さん
気付いて…
You went overboard with everything.
何がも何も…
You're trying to make Kohei jealous, right?
耕平の嫉妬心を
あおろうとしてるんでしょ？
Yeah!
（寿･時田）よっしゃあ！
（笑い声）
Is that good? You're crying?
（愛菜）それ おもしろい？
（耕平）うう…
（愛菜）えっ 泣いてんの!?
It's our turn to cook.
さて 俺たちの料理の番だが…
Why are you so far away?
なぜ そんなに距離を取る？
Even if I practice, it's hard doing it on my own.
（伊織）しかし 練習するにしても
独力では難しいな
Should I tell her what's going on and ask her to help?
こいつには 事情を話して
手伝ってもらうべきか
Hey, Chisa.
（伊織）なあ 千紗…
（千紗）うっ！　何？
-What?
-Actually...
（伊織）実は…
（千紗）ん？
I'll get some tea.
お茶でも飲もっと
That's the issue.
というわけなんだ
So that's what's going on.
そういうことだったんだ
So, Chisa, to help me practice...
だからさ 千紗 練習に―
will you go out with me?
つきあってくれないか
（愛菜）プハッ…
What's going on? Why did Iori just ask Chisa that?
えっ？　えっ？
どういうこと？
伊織が千紗に？　どうして？
お… 落ち着こう
Calm down. I might have gotten the wrong idea,
just like when we were shopping.
買い物のときみたいに
誤解かもしれないし…
-Are you serious?
-Yeah. I'm serious.
（千紗）本気なの？
（伊織）ああ 本気だ
-I've fallen in love.
-I don't have the wrong idea!
俺も 好きになってるからな
（愛菜）誤解じゃなーい！
でも 千紗 この前―
But, Chisa...
You said you could never imagine dating him...
あんなの 相手に
考えられないって…
-Really? I'm glad.
-No!
そっか… うれしい
（愛菜）イヤー！
-Are you sure you're okay with me?
-Yeah. You're the only one.
（千紗）でも 私でいいの？
ああ お前しかいないんだ
What's wrong, Cakey?
どうした？　ケバ子
（愛菜）ち… 千紗と伊織が…
-Chisa and Iori...
-What happened to them?
やつらがどうした？
She was against it until just a few days ago!
（愛菜）この前までは
イヤがってたはずなのに～！
What are you talking about?
なんの話だ？
（愛菜）私の口からは言いたくな…
（食べる音）
I don't want to talk about it.
I bet you just have the wrong idea again.
（耕平）どうせ また
くだらない勘違いだろうに
If you don't have any weights, you'll float.
It'll be hard to practice.
（千紗）
でも ウエイトがないと―
体が浮いて 練習しにくいかも
Then we can just put heavy things on me.
（伊織）だったら
俺の体に重い物とかを―
縛ってくれないか
Can you tie me up?
（耕平）んん!?
What's going on? Is what Cakey said just now true?
どういうことだ？
まさか さっき
ケバ子が言っていたのは…
Was she talking about the awakening of a sexual fetish?
特殊性癖の目覚めという意味か！
No. I can't tell from just that one sentence.
いや だが さっきの
ひと言だけでは断定は…
That's kind of dangerous.
（千紗）それは
ちょっと危ないかな
I see. Then can you at least...
（伊織）そうか
だったら せめて…
（耕平）もう一度 事実確認を…
I have to confirm the truth!
...step on me with all your strength?
思い切り 俺を踏んでくれ
（耕平）ハハハ… んん!?
ど… どうだった？
How was it?
You're right...
お前の言うとおりだった
I never imagined he'd awaken...
まさか あいつが
目覚めていたとは…
I see. So he did awaken.
そっか やっぱ
目覚めてたんだ…
I'm back!
ただいま
（梓）おかえり
-Welcome back.
-Sorry I'm late.
遅くなってごめんね
夕飯は大丈夫？
-Is dinner okay?
-No problem.
平気平気 ちょうど今
私たちの番になったところだから
-It's our turn now.
-I'm glad I'm on time.
間に合ってよかった
Dinner is fine, but...
ただ そっちはいいんだけどさ
（奈々華）ん？
（千紗）んっ…
（愛菜）ん…
（耕平）ああ…
（伊織）ん？
For some reason,
Iori and the others are acting strange.
（梓）なぜか 伊織たちが
妙な空気になってんだよね
（奈々華）ん？
（時田）伊織
-Iori?
-What did you do?
お前 何やったんだ？
Nothing in particular.
（伊織）特に何も
（愛菜の寝息）
ん…
あ… あれ？　千紗？
Chisa?
Sorry to ask you to come.
（伊織）悪いな
つきあってもらっちまって
That's Iori's voice.
あれ？　伊織の声…
What if--? Are they trying to sneak in
some alone time since they're dating now?
まさか あの２人―
つきあい始めたからって
人目を忍んで…
I'm going to get wet.
（千紗）ぬれちゃう…
You should take off your clothes.
（伊織）服は 脱いだほうが…
（愛菜）ヒッ！
Okay, I'm taking my clothes off.
（千紗）分かった 脱ぐ
-Okay. Let's do it.
-What?
（伊織）よし じゃあ やるぞ
な… な… 何やって！
What are you doing?
ほんとに何やってんのー！
ケ… ケバ子
貴様 ここで何を!?
Cakey! What are you doing here?
That's what I was about to say!
（愛菜）それ
こっちのセリフなんだけど！
You were acting weird. Now you're doing weird things!
様子が変だと思ったら
行動まで変だなんて！
あ… これはその…
プールに財布を落としてだな
This is-- I dropped my wallet in the pool.
Liar!
（愛菜）ウソばっかり！
Iori, tell me the truth.
伊織 正直に言って
You've been hiding something since yesterday, right?
昨日から
隠してること あるんでしょ
（伊織）うっ… しかたない
正直に言うか
It's no use. I'll tell you the truth.
-Cakey...
-Yeah?
（伊織）ケバ子
（愛菜）うん
We're practicing diving.
実はこれ ダイビングの練習なんだ
Why won't you tell me the truth?
どうして 正直に
言ってくれないの！
I did tell you the truth!
正直に言ったんだが!?
You're engaged in some sort of advanced adult activity!
だって 明らかに 上級者向けの
変なことしてたじゃない！
No, this is for beginners.
いや むしろ
初級者向けなんだ
Aina, we really are practicing diving.
愛菜 これ 本当に
ダイビングの練習だから
（愛菜）え？　そうなの？
-Really?
-Why do you believe it when Chisa says it?
なぜ千紗だと ひと言で信じる
We were practicing mask clearing.
（伊織）ってことで
マスククリアの練習をな
I see.
そ… そっかあ　それなら
最初から そう言ってくれたら
Then you should have told me earlier.
I didn't want you to laugh at me.
お前らに笑われるのは
しゃくだからな
I wouldn't laugh at you!
I would've helped you if you had told me.
笑わないよ むしろ
言ってくれたら手伝うのに
-Really?
-That'd be a big help.
マジか！
（千紗）助かるかも
So, what should I do?
（愛菜）
それで 何をしたらいいの？
Oh, well, then...
（伊織）おう それじゃ…
（男性）フゥ… お？
（伊織のもがく声）
-Don't struggle!
-Stop kicking!
（千紗）暴れないの！
（愛菜）ジタバタしないで！
Hello. Is this the police?
もしもし 警察ですか…
There's still water in my mask.
（伊織）いまだに
マスクに水が残るなあ
You're almost there.
あと少しって感じなんだけどね
Maybe you're still afraid of the water.
まだ 水を怖がってるのかも
It's come down to this. Let's do it.
よし こうなりゃ アレやるか
It?
アレ？
（千紗）うっ…
ああ 前にやった方法なんだが…
Yeah. We did it before.
I'm in a bathtub.
（伊織）ここは風呂
ここは風呂…
I'm in a bathtub.
前にもやったの？
（千紗）私は無関係だから
-You did this before?
-I had nothing to do with it.
Does that really work?
（愛菜）
それ 本当に効果あるの？
-No. It didn't work at all.
-What?
いや まったくなかった
（愛菜）はあ？
じゃあ なんでやるのよ
Then why are you doing it?
I thought...
（伊織）ここなら―
I'd be able to get closer here.
アレがもっと近くで
見られるかもしれないからな
I want to do everything I can.
やれることは
全部やっておきたいんだ
（愛菜）ん？
Anyway, you can go to sleep.
ってわけで 先に寝ててくれ
（千紗）分かった
-Okay.
-Don't overdo it.
あんたも ほどほどに
しなさいよ
Thanks for coming.
つきあってくれて
サンキューな
-Goodnight.
じゃ おやすみ
（千紗）おやすみ
Yeah, good night.
（伊織）おう おやすみ
（ドアが閉まる音）
Well, then...
さてと
プハッ！　ハァ…
All right. Not bad.
よし こんなもんだろ
Excuse me.
（男性）あの すみません
（伊織）ん？
I'm from the police.
（警官）警察の者ですが
（伊織）うっ！
Someone reported a girl and a guy
engaging in unusual behavior.
（警官）非行に走る男女がいるとの
通報がありまして
ああ… いやあ
何かの間違いじゃないですかね
Well... I think there's been a mistake.
I didn't see anyone suspicious.
怪しい人なんて
誰も見ませんでしたよ ハハハ…
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
そうですか
（伊織）ええ
I didn't see any dangerous people like that.
そんな危ない人なんて 影も形も…
（警官）ふむ…
Just in case, I'm going to look around
to make sure there's no one suspicious here.
念のため 怪しい人物がいないか
この辺を見回りますね
わ… 分かりました
I understand.
クッ… うっ！
I can't get out.
（伊織）出るに出られん…
（鳥の鳴き声）
You're saying Iori's in bed because he caught a cold?
で 伊織は風邪で倒れたと
That's right.
そうみたい
When I woke up, his face was red.
起きたら 隣で赤い顔してて
びっくりしたよ
I was surprised.
-Iori's always like that!
-Even the way idiots get sick is different.
さすが 伊織だ
バカは 風邪のひき方も
ひと味 違いますねえ
His fever isn't that high, so I think he'll be okay.
そこまで熱はないから
大丈夫だとは思うけどね
He can't participate in today's lessons.
今日の実習は無理だな
It's because of what I said.
私が 変なこと
言っちゃったから…
いやいやいや 奈々華さんに
責任はないと思います
No, it's not your fault.
This is obviously his own fault.
奇行は 明らかに
やつ自身の責任ですから
Anyway...
（時田）まっ そういうわけでだ
Let's let Iori sleep.
（寿）伊織のやつは
寝かせておくとしよう
Aina and Kohei have to concentrate
on getting their licenses.
（梓）愛菜と耕平は 自分の
ライセンス取得に集中しないとね
-Yes!
-Okay.
（愛菜）はーい
（耕平）了解です
（伊織の寝息）
ん… ああ…
うーん 一眠りしたら
すっきりしたな…
I feel better after sleeping.
（ドアが開く音）
（伊織）あ…
Oh, you look like you're feeling better, Iori.
（梓）おっ
具合よさそうだね 伊織
Azusa, you didn't go diving?
梓さん ダイビングに
行かなかったんですか？
-Yeah.
-Sorry. It's my fault.
（梓）まあね
（伊織）すみません 俺のせいで
What are you talking about?
（梓）なんのなんの
So, how are you feeling?
（梓）それで 調子はどう？
I'm feeling much better.
（伊織）
もう ほとんど回復しました
It'd be best if you took some medicine,
本当は 薬も飲んでおくべき
なんだけど―
but the pharmacy isn't open.
薬屋が開いてなくてね
There's no need for that.
そこまでしなくても
（梓）ダメだよ 伊織
No, Iori!
明日以降も海に入るんだから
きっちり治さないと
You're going in the ocean tomorrow.
So, you have to fully recover.
はあ…
（梓）で 薬はなかったけど―
They didn't have any medicine,
but they had this.
これがあったからさ
（伊織）ん？
（伊織）ぬう…
Azusa, what's that?
梓さん これは…
ん？　有名な民間療法 知らない？
A famous home remedy. You don't know it?
（伊織）知っている
知ってはいるが―
I know. I do know.
The only problem is...
問題なのは
１と２ どっちなのかだ
Is it number 1 or 2?
All right, Iori.
じゃあ 伊織…
（伊織）は… はい
Yes?
Stick out your neck.
首 出して
（伊織）ハァ…
Good, it's number 1!
（伊織）よかった １のほうか
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
どうかした？
（伊織）いえ なんでもないです
-Here. Okay.
-Thank you.
はい ＯＫ
ありがとうございま… ん？
ANOTHER ONE
Can you pull down your pants next?
じゃ 次は
ズボン 下ろしてくれる？
No, a combination technique!
（伊織）イヤー！　合わせ技！
あ… 梓さん
そこまでする必要は！
Azusa, you don't have to do this for me!
No, no. There's no medicine.
ダメダメ　薬 ないんだから
これくらいしないと
So we have to do this.
（伊織）うう… いかん
このままでは―
No. If I don't do something,
something else other than my health
is going to be destroyed!
健康とは別の何かを損なう！
（梓）あっ！
I'm going to look for some other medicine!
（伊織）ほかに 薬に
なりそうな物を探してきます！
（鳥の鳴き声）
This is perfect for medicine, right?
（伊織）これ 薬として
完璧じゃないですかね
True. It disinfects, stimulates perspiration,
and induces sleep.
（梓）確かに　滅菌作用
発汗作用 誘眠作用があって―
It's also rich in nutrients.
栄養豊富…
It's the best medicine!
（伊織）さすがは 百薬の長！
Sick people shouldn't drink it though.
病人が飲む物じゃないと
思うけどねえ
But, if I drink now and fall sleep,
I won't be able to sleep at night.
（伊織）けど 今 酒飲んで寝たら
夜また 眠れなくなるか
You haven't been able to sleep at night anyway.
ただでさえ
夜 眠れてないみたいだしね
That's for a different reason.
それは また
別の理由ですけど…
A different reason?
別の理由って？
You know...
いや だってほら 梓さんと
奈々華さんが隣で寝てれば―
I feel nervous sleeping next to you and Nanaka,
so I can't fall asleep.
普通 緊張して眠れませんよ
Oh, I didn't know that.
ありゃ そうだったか
それは悪いことしたね
Sorry about that.
（梓）うーん…
（伊織）梓さん？
Azusa?
-Hey, Iori.
-Yes?
（梓）じゃあさ 伊織
（伊織）はい
Do you want to have sex?
エッチしよっか
ブハッ！
（せき込み）
はあ？　何を急に!?
-What are you saying!?
-You won't be nervous anymore, right?
そしたら
緊張しなくなるでしょ？
いやいやいや！　そんな軽々と
することじゃないかと！
No! It's not something to do so casually!
むう… 失礼な
That's so rude.
I don't do it with just any guy.
私だって そこらの
変な男とはしないよ
あ…
But I do like you.
でも 伊織のことは
気に入ってるからね
I'm fine with doing it once.
１回くらい いいかな
（伊織）
なんというスポーツ感覚
She's acting like it's a sport!
I'm half joking.
（梓）なんて 半分冗談だよ
It'd be bad if things got awkward between us.
それでギクシャクしたら
つまらないしね
は… 半分？
Half?
Yeah. Half.
（梓）そう… 半分
If you seriously want to do it, I'm okay with that.
本気で したいって言うなら
いいけど？
（心臓の音）
（伊織）た… 試されてる
I'm being tested!
I'm...
俺 今…
really...
すげえ 試されてる！
being tested right now!
（早まる心臓の音）
I'm...
や…
going to say no.
めときます…
アハハ… そりゃ残念
That's too bad.
By the way, Azusa...
（伊織）ところで 梓さん
（梓）ん？
You like Tokita as well as Nanaka, right?
奈々華さん以外に―
That's right.
Why don't you go after Tokita?
なら 時田先輩に
アプローチはしないんですか？
（梓）うーん トッキーは
なんて言うかさ…
Tokki is kind of, you know...
I'd be wasting my time chasing him.
不毛な恋愛じゃない
So it's different with Nanaka?
（伊織）奈々華さん相手は
違うのだろうか
A waste of time? Why?
不毛って どうして？
（梓）あれ 伊織は知らないの？
（伊織）何を？
Don't you know, Iori?
-What?
-Tokki, you know...
（梓）だって トッキーはさ
has a girlfriend.
彼女いるんだよ
は？
-He has a girlfriend?
-Yeah. A girlfriend.
あの人に彼女？
（梓）うん 彼女
-A homosexual?
-Why would she be homosexual?
ホモの？
（梓）どうしてそうなるかな？
ホモサピエンスの？
Homo sapiens?
（梓）あっ 聞いてたのは種族か
ちゃんと人間だよ
So you were asking about her species?
She is a human.
I see. Tokita has a girlfriend!
そっか 時田先輩に彼女ですか
That's right!
そうなんだよねえ
（梓･伊織）アハハハ
-Let's drink.
-What's wrong all of a sudden?
飲みましょう！
（梓）急にどうしたの？
（伊織）チクショー！　どうして
あの人にできて 俺には！
Darn! Why does he have a girlfriend but not me?
Wow, you're drinking a lot!
（梓）おっ いい飲みっぷりだね！
アハハ！
（伊織）ウォッカー！
（耕平）フン…
（愛菜と耕平の笑い声）
Congratulations on getting your license.
ライセンス取得 おめでとう
You're real divers now.
これで お前らも
立派なダイバーだな
-Congratulations.
-I'm not sure about her though.
おめでとう
こいつは 怪しい気がしますけど
こ… これからうまくなるし！
-I'm going to get better!
-That's the right attitude!
ハハハ その意気だ
All right! We're going to Miyakojima tomorrow!
（時田）よし！
いよいよ 明日は宮古島(みやこじま)だ！
（一同の歓声）
Let's have a toast first!
んじゃ まずは祝杯を…
ん？
（一同）あ…
（梓のいびき）
うう…
It looks like they already did.
（時田）
先に あげていたみたいだな
He's all better. Good.
すっかり治ったようで
何よりだ
Oh, dear. They're so impatient!
（奈々華）あらあら 気が早いわね
（愛菜･千紗）ハァ…
A masochist...
（耕平）Ｍ…
♪～
DEEP BLUE AL FINE
KAYA MIZUKI
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of arpeggio
If life sparkles only to the beat
Of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
～♪
Thanks, everybody!
（カヤ）
みんな ありがとう！
Yeah!
（部員たち）うおおお！
（伊織･耕平）うわっ！
（耕平･伊織）グッ…
Hey, don't act so crazy, freshman.
（時田）おいおい
そう はしゃぐなよ １年坊
All right. Let's begin.
さあ 始めようか…
NEXT EPISODE
"OTORI"